curata.com 2018-12-20

# 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**www.curata.com/t//privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. Therefore, we are committed to respecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal data and content. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we use and safeguards the information you provide in using the Service.  In this Privacy Policy, Â“Terms of ServiceÂ” means our Terms of Service applicable from time to time and currently found at www.curata.com/t//tos. Â“Personal DataÂ” means any information that we possess relating to an identified or identifiable user of the Service; other capitalized terms have the meanings given them in the Terms of Service.

**What information do we collect?**

In order to provide you with access to the Service, we may gather and process some or all of the following information:

**Content:** any information that is collected or stored by or from users of the Service, other than Registration Information, Customer Service Communications or Log Information.Â  Content includes information obtained from using the service to find materials available from third parties on the internet (Â“External ContentÂ”) .Â  Content also includes internal analytics relating to your Content, and information obtained through integration with your content management systems, email and marketing automation systems, such as sales leads or other contacts (Â“Internal ContentÂ”). ****

**Registration Information:** any information provided when voluntarily registering for use of the Service, including, but not limited to, username and password and email address. ****

**Customer Service Communications:** any information that is reported to us about the operation of the Service, including bug reports or requests for enhancements. ****

**Log Information:** When you use some services, our servers automatically record basic information that your application sends. These server logs may include information such as your message, Internet Protocol address, other addressing information, the date and time of your request and an authentication token used to validate the identity of you and your computer. ****

**How do we use this information and for what purpose?**

Our primary purpose in collecting information is to provide you with an efficient user experience.  We may use the information defined in this Privacy Policy to: provide the services and any customer support you request; resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; enforce our Terms of Service; customize, measure, and improve the Service, content and layout; if you choose to opt-in, inform you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; compare information for accuracy, and verify your identity; provide other services for you as described when we collect the information. Additionally we may use your information as described below.

**Registration Information:** We ask for Registration Information in order to verify your identity and to enable your use of the Service.  We may use third party banking organizations and other providers of payment services to bill you, and in that case we will, therefore, provide this billing provider with the necessary billing data. ****

We respect the privacy of personal e-mail accounts and we will store your e-mail addresses just as securely as other Personal Data.  We will not send you unwanted e-mail messages or junk mail, and your details will not be passed to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit permission.  However, we will use e-mail to send you messages about faults and service issues.  We may also use e-mail to keep you up to date with news about the Service.  If you do not want to be kept informed in this way by e-mail, please contact us at Curata, Inc., 92 Montvale Avenue, Suite 2500, Stoneham, MA 02180.  In any event, we reserve the right to use e-mail to notify you of any claims related to your use of the Service, including without limitation claims of violation of third party rights.

**Content:** In general, we will not use, review or provide third parties access to your Content except as specifically authorized by you.Â  In particular, we normally provide access to Internal Content only to your authorized users (or exchanged with other systems such as a content management system for which you have authorized access).   However, if required by law, we reserve the right to pre-screen, review, flag, filter, modify, refuse or remove any or all Content from the Service. ****

**Customer Service Communications:** Information which is voluntarily submitted in feedback is used for the purposes of reviewing this feedback and improving the Service.  We reserve the right to utilize anonymous information for marketing purposes, for instance by displaying selected comments on our website or in other communications.  Further, we may from time to time ask you to provide information on your experience which will be used to measure and improve quality.  You are at no time in any obligation to provide any of such data. We will never use any personally identifiable (feedback) information without your explicit permission thereto.

**Log Information:** We will use this routing information to provide you with access to the Service and for statistical information. ****

**To whom do we transfer your personal information?**

Except as provided below, we shall not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any Registration Information or Content to any third party without your explicit permission, unless we are obliged to do so under applicable laws or by order of the competent authorities.  

We may share your information with our affiliates and other service providers.  We may offer some of our services in connection with other service providers.  Registration Information that you provide to us may be sent to those providers in order to deliver the service provided by them; similarly, personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to operate the Service.

Information collected by us may be stored and processed in any country in which we and our affiliates maintain facilities.  We reserve the right to transfer information outside of the country where you reside and/or from which you use the Service.  By using the Service you consent to any such transfer of information.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions as well as in the event all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, personal information of our users will generally be one of the transferred business assets. We reserve the right to include your personal information, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party.

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service, we may access, use, preserve or disclose any information we have access to if we have a good faith belief that such access, use, preservation or disclosure of any information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**How do we protect your personal information?**

We take appropriate organizational and technical measures to protect the data provided to us or collected by us, and do not retain it any longer than permitted in order to perform our services or as required under relevant legislation, with due observance of the applicable obligations and exceptions under the relevant legislation.  You should be aware that internet communications are not always secure.  We cannot promise you that third parties cannot access your Content; in this regard, you are responsible for maintaining the security and confidentiality of your account passwords.  It is a condition of your use that you agree we are not liable for any such disclosure.

**How long is your personal data kept by us?**

We will retain your information for as long as is necessary to: (1) provide the use of the Service; (2) invoice to you your use of the Service and to maintain records until invoicing for the Service cannot be lawfully challenged and legal proceedings may no longer be pursued; (3) communicate with you regarding other services that we offer; (4) comply with applicable legislation, regulatory requests and relevant orders from competent courts; (5) enforce our Terms of Service; or (6) fulfill any of the other purposes detailed in this Privacy Policy.

**What are cookies and how do we use them?**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the userÂ’s hard drive containing information about the user.  Usage of a cookie will in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our website.  For instance, by setting a cookie on our website, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our website.  If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our website.  The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our website.  Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our website.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Service.  However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**How far does our responsibility extend?**

This Privacy Policy applies to services that are owned and operated by us.  It does not necessarily apply to sites our customers create using our software, even if operated by us.  We do not exercise control over other users or third party websites that may link to our Service.  They may place their own or other files on their website, collect data or solicit personal information from you.  We accept no responsibility or liability for these other sites or services.

**Can this Privacy Policy be modified?**

We reserve the right to modify the provisions of this Privacy Policy if deemed necessary. We will inform you of these changes by publishing the revised Privacy Policy at www.curata.com/t/privacy.  The revised Privacy Policy shall become effective within thirty (30) days of such publishing, unless you expressly accept the revised statement earlier by clicking on the accept button.  You agree that the express acceptance by you, or your continued use of the Service after the notice period of thirty (30) days, shall constitute your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

**What rights do you have and how can you contact us?**

If you would like to exercise your right to view, correct, complete or remove your Personal Data, please contact us at privacy@curata.com. Upon verification of your identity, we will attempt to quickly fulfill your request, provided we will not act contrary to applicable legislation by fulfilling your request.

We provide individuals the opportunity to â€œopt-outâ€ of having their personally identifiable information collected by us. In addition, European data protection legislation gives individuals the right to access personally identifiable information held about them. Individuals may ensure that such information is accurate and relevant for the purposes for which we collected it. Individuals may review their own information and correct or remove any information that is incorrect, as permitted by applicable law. To request opt-out, review, modification or removal of personal data, you should submit a written request to us at [privacy@curata.com](mailto:privacy@curata.com).
